sheckys.com 2019-05-24

# Privacy Policy | Sheckys.com

### Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

(1) What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

[(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including [your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views]);]

[(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services.

[(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including email address);]

[(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters

[(e) any other information that you choose to send to us; and]

[(f) OTHER INFORMATION.]

[(2) Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We [may] use [both] [“session” cookies] [and “persistent” cookies] on the website. [We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and [OTHER USES].] [We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; [OTHER USES].]

[Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.] [Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.]

[We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: //www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.]

[Our [advertisers/payment services providers] may also send you cookies.]

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites [, including this one].]

(3) Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

[(a) administer the website;]

[(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;]

[(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;]

[(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;]

[(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;]

[(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;]

[(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;]

[(h) send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications (relating to our business [or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications) ;]

[(i) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;]

[(j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;]

[Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.]

[We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.]

[All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Dalpay. You should only provide your personal information to Dalpay after reviewing the Dalpay privacy policy (available at www.dalpay.is). We will share information with Dalpay only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.]

(4) Other disclosures

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

[(d) to any of our agents, suppliers or subcontractors (but only as reasonably necessary for our purposes as set out above); and]

[(e) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.]

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

[(5) International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries [(including [the United States], [Japan], [OTHER COUNTRIES])] which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA.

[In addition, [personal information that you submit for publication on the website] will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.]

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

(6) Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

[We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted [using SSL technology].]

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

[You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.]

(7) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

[We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.]

(8) Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at $10.00).

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

(9) Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

(10) Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

(11) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, [please write to us by email](https://www.sheckys.com/contact-us/)

(12) Data controller

The data controller responsible for our website is [ROSEBUD ENTERTAINMENT].

## Disclaimer

By accessing this website – Sheckys (hereafter written as “SHECKYS.COM” ) and affiliated Websites, you, the user, (hereafter “You”) and we, the owners and all employees of Sheckys (hereafter “We”) are entering a binding agreement to the following Terms and Conditions of Use.

We do not endorse any information posted by Users and we are not liable for any such information posted on our site, including but not limited to any information posted about you.

We reserve the right to take any action with respect to information posted on our site which we believe is appropriate in our sole discretion with respect to such information, including but not limited to termination of this Agreement. However, We cannot, nor do, control the information provided by Users or other content providers which is made available through our system. By its very nature, other people’s information may be offensive, harmful, inaccurate, or in some cases may be mislabeled or deceptively labeled.

You acknowledge and agree We shall not be held responsible in any way for the outcome of any contact or meeting, whether in person, by telephone or any other means, resulting from advertisements placed or responded to, or messages or communications sent or received by Users or Advertisers through SHECKYS.COM, or through any use, directly or indirectly, of SHECKYS.

You further acknowledge and agree that We do not screen any Users or Advertisers, have no control over their actions and makes no representations or warranties with respect to the character, veracity, age, health or any other attribute of Users of SHECKYS, including any person who places Advertisements in the Website.

You further acknowledge and agree that We do not endorse, encourage, recommend or arrange communications or meetings among Users, or any other persons, and You are expected to use common sense and take appropriate measures and precautions to insure Your own personal safety and privacy in the event that You choose to communicate with, or meet with any person with whom you have communicated through the use of the public areas or chat areas of SHECKYS, or through advertisements posted on SHECKYS.

The entire risk as to the quality and performance of the Materials and all services provided by SHECKYS is borne by You. Some states do not allow exclusions of an implied warranty, so this disclaimer may not apply to You and You may have other legal rights that vary from state to state or by jurisdiction.

By accessing SHECKYS. You agree that you will not use SHECKYS as a means to purchase or solicit illegal activities. You further agree to comply with any and all local, county, district, state, and federal laws in the event you subsequently have any interaction with anyone or any entity you become acquanted with as a consequence of your participation on this Site.

We are not liable for damages resulting from disseminating, failing to disseminate, or incorrectly or inaccurately disseminating any Materials, data, advertisement or other communication at or through the Websites.

You acknowledge that use of SHECKYS is at Your own risk. We do not represent or endorse the accuracy of reliability of any advice, opinion, statement or other information displayed, uploaded or distributed through the Websites or by a User of the Websites or any other person or entity.

Information on SHECKYS, whether posted by us, other Users, or third parties, is provided “AS IS” and may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors.

You agree to engage in a good faith effort to resolve any and all disputes pertaining to use of SHECKYS or this Disclaimer before resorting to litigation. Any dispute or claim that cannot be resolved by such good faith efforts shall be resolved by binding arbitration before a certified Arbiter in Nevada, USA. You, the User, hereby acknowledge and consent to jurisdiction of the United States and agree that the venue for all dispute resolution shall be within the State of Nevada.
